harmonhomes.com 2013-05-21

# Harmonhomes.com - Privacy Policy < Page < Harmonhomes.com

### 1\. What information is collected?

#### * Personal Information:

We may require personal contact information and home information from some of our members. The information is used to effectively and accurately create, maintain, and display Harmon Homes's classified services. The required home information varies with each site of the Harmon Homes network depending on the industry and its relevant data. You do not have to give us personally identifiable information in order to visit our website, however, on the Website, you may be able to order products, enter contests, participate in a survey or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. Personally identifiable information is generally provided and collected when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with our service department. As a result of those actions, you may supply us with such information as your name, address, phone numbers, e-mail address, contact preferences, credit card information, financial information and information relating to a support or service issue that may, alone or in combination with other data, constitute personally identifiable information. If we collect personally identifiable information from you, you are giving us permission to use that information for the specific purpose for which it is provided and to contact you regarding site services, improve or enhance site performance, to offer you information regarding products and services, fulfill product orders, improve our Website, to communicate to you about other matters that may be of interest to you and for any other purpose described in this Privacy Policy. In connection with the foregoing, we may share your information with our affiliates. Users unwilling to provide personally identifiable information online can choose to work with a sales representative or customer service representative to utilize member services or other site offerings. We also aggregate data from multiple users in a manner that is not personally identifiable and use such data as we deem appropriate.

#### * Cookies:

Some sites in the Harmon Homes network utilize cookies in order to provide members and merchants with a more personalized experience by remembering who you are when you revisit the site. Cookies also track visitor activity and traffic patterns among the sites so that we can identify users' interests and behavior. With this information, we can improve existing user services and develop new products appropriate for our audience. Cookies are text files placed in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Website. However, once you choose to furnish our Website with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. When you visit our Websites, third party vendors and advertisers also place or read cookies on your Internet browser. This is a common practice on the Internet; these cookies may be used to determine whether you have visited other Websites, to measure the effectiveness of advertising and links on other Websites, and to provide you with information of potential interest to you, among other purposes. This is not an exhaustive list of all uses of cookies on our Websites. Most Web browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can, however, set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

### 2\. How is the information collected?

* Some members are requested to submit personal and home information using the online Email Notify, or other online services. Users unwilling to pass personal information online can choose to work with a sales representative or customer service representative to utilize member services. Sometimes we may use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to monitor user traffic patterns, analyze and quantify user preferences, improve the design and content of our Website, and enable us to personalize your user experience. All such usage data shall be the exclusive property of this Website.

### 3\. How information will be used?

#### * Resale and Disclosure of Information

Harmon Media Group is not in the business of selling personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their commercial use. We do reserve the right to disclose some personal information collected on our site to third parties. We may provide third parties with non-exclusive, limited use of Harmon Media Group's collected information in order for the third party to promote and market the third party's service. Any right of the third party to distribute, transfer, transmit, or re-sell Harmon Media Group's information is prohibited.

#### * Privacy of Harmon Homes Email Lists

We collect and record personal information in order to maintain email lists. We utilize the emails to keep members informed of the site services, site performance, promotions, and offer information regarding industry related services and products.

### 4\. User choices in receiving and distribution of information

#### * Harmon Homes Email Lists

Real estate professionals may receive monthly emails informing them of special promotions and advertising tips. Real estate professionals wishing not receive the mailer can send a request via email to be removed from the mailing list. Real estate professional members automatically receive an email to confirm their placement on our site and to give them the necessary information to edit and delete their classified ads. They also receive notification of ad renewal opportunities. Harmon Media Group reserves the right to include third party advertisements that provide additional services to members in the confirmation emails. We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products and services that may be of interest to you. If you have signed up to receive our e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this Website, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this Website.

#### * Third Party Distribution

Real estate professionals may receive information directly from third parties that have related services. Real Estate professionals that do not wish to receive the third party information can opt-out of the service at the time they place an ad with Harmon Homes. Third parties receive only the needed personal information in order to effectively target members' needs and interests. Third parties have non-exclusive, limited use of the information provided by Harmon Media Group. Any right of the third party to distribute, transfer, transmit, or re-sell Harmon Media Groups' information is prohibited.

### 5\. Data Security

#### * Personal Information

To protect the member's account information, Harmon Homes assigns each member with either a unique user name or password or a unique ID number. These unique identifiers are disclosed to the user via email immediately upon joining the Harmon Homes network. Only members have the ability to modify their personal information and delete their ads as needed.

#### * Credit Card Transactions

Harmon Homes uses PayPal/Verisign Certification and secure servers to transmit all online credit card transaction in an encrypted format.

### 6\. Data Quality and Access

* Members may access their information 24 hours a day using their designated user name and password or ad ID number. Members may modify or delete their information as needed.

### 7\. Usage Terms

*Access to and use of this Website is subject to compliance with this Website's Terms of Use.

### 8\. Our Commitment to Security

*We have in place what we believe to be reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the personally identifiable information we collect and help prevent unauthorized access and use of such data.

### 9\. Third Party Online Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to show you advertisements tailored to your interests on this and other Websites and other interactive media and/or to keep track of your response to each ad.

### 10\. Information on Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers and Sponsors

*Our Website may contain links to other Websites whose information practices may be different than ours. While visiting this Website, you may link to another Website via a window opened within (or on top of) our Website. Our privacy policies and procedures may or may not be consistent with the policies and procedures of other Websites you visit while here. Users should consult, read and understand any other Website's privacy notices before choosing to provide personally identifiable data on such linked Website as our privacy policies and treatment of your data does not apply and we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

### 11\. Privacy Policy Changes

*We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting, unless otherwise indicated. We have no duty or obligation to inform prior visitors that changes have been made, regardless of the scope and importance of the changes. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Website after such changes are posted will be deemed to constitute your agreement to and acceptance of such changes.

### 12\. Questions

* If you have further questions that were not addressed in the above privacy policy, please contact Harmon Media Group Legal Department at 4501 Hills & Dales Rd. NW, Canton, OH 44708.
